Jeremiah Wadsworth papers
Connecticut Historical Society
- IV. Wadsworth and Carter papers, 1780-1787
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, October-December 1780 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, January-February 1781 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, March-April 1781 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, May-June 15, 1781 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, June 16-30, 1781 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, July 1-20, 1781 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, July 21-31, 1781 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, August 1781 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, September 1-15, 1781 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, September 16-30, 1781 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, October 1781 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 1781 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 1-15, 1781 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 16-31, 1781 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, January-February, 1782 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, March 1782 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, April 1-15, 1782 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, April 16-30, 1782 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, May-July 1782 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, August-September 10, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, September 11-30, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, October 1-10, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, October 11-19, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, October 20-31, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 1-10, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 11-16, 1782 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 17-18, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 19, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 20, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 21, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 22, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 23, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 24, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 25, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 26, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 27, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 28, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 29, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November 30, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 1, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 2, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 3-4, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 5, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 6, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 7-8, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 9, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 10, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 11, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 12, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 13, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 14-15, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 16, 1782 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 17, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 18, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 19-20, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 21-22, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 23-24, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 25, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 26, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 27, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 28, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 29, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 30, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, December 31, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, 1782 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, ca. 1782 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, January 1-15, 1783 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, January 16-31, 1783 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, February-March 1783 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, April-May 1783 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, June-October 1783 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, November-December 1783 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, 1784 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, undated (1 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter receipts, undated (2 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter cash book, 1780-1781 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter accounts, 1780-1782 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter copy book of bills, May-July1781 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter waste book, July-December 1781 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter account book, April-June 1782 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter waste book, April-June 1782 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Wadsworth and Carter account book, August-September 1782 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Wadsworth and Carter accounts, November 1782 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Wadsworth and Carter accounts, December 1782 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Wadsworth and Carter cash accounts, December 1782 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Wadsworth and Carter accounts of rations issued, October, December 1782 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Wadsworth and Carter account book, 1782-1783 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Wadsworth and Carter accounts, 1783 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Wadsworth and Carter waste book, 1783-1784 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth and Carter accounts, 1784 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Wadsworth and Carter documents in French, 1784 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Wadsworth and Carter bills and legal documents, 1785-1787 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- V. Historical and Genealogical Information, 1804-1890s
  - Inventory of Wadsworth Estate, 1804, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - John F. Morris correspondence regarding Trumbull estate, 1837, 1882, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - John F. Morris correspondence regarding the estates of Jeremiah and Daniel Wadsworth and portraits of the two men, 1878-1893 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Wadsworth family genealogical and historical information, ca. 1880s, 1892; handwritten copies of Jeremiah Wadsworth correspondence, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1882, 1885, 1890, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - John F. Morris notebook, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Letter with a description by John Trumbull of his portrait of Daniel and Jeremiah Wadsworth, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Abstract of correspondence of Jeremiah Wadsworth, by George Clinton Fairchild Williams, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Handwritten copy of 1775 Jeremiah Wadsworth diary, notes (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Notebook with handwritten copies of Jeremiah Wadsworth correspondence from 1778-1801 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten copies of Jeremiah Wadsworth correspondence from 1779-1804 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Handwritten copies of Jeremiah Wadsworth correspondence from 1770s-1790; copy of Daniel Wadsworth’s record of deeds on Talcott Mountain from 1805-1848 (Box 50, Folder 12)